Section 51 of Anthology of Modern Indian Poetry
All Librevox recordings are in the public domain.
For more information or to volunteer, please visit
Librevox.org
Anthology of Modern Indian Poetry by Gwendolyn Goodwin
I shall not try to flee the sword of death
nor fearing it a watchful vigil keep.
It will be nothing but a sigh, a breath, a turning on the other side to sleep.
Through all the clothes and tanglements of earth,
my spirit shaking off its bonds shall fare and pass,
and rise in new unfettered birth, escaping from this labyrinth of care.
Within the mortar caravan said I, no rest and no abiding place I know,
I linger here for but a fleeting day and at the morrow's summoning I go.
What are these bonds that try to shackle me through all their intricate chains my way I find?
I travel like a wandering melody that floats untamed and taken on the wind.
From an unsympathetic world I flee to you your love and fellowship I crave.
Oh, singers dead, sawdha and mushafi, I lay my song
distribute on your grave. End of poem by Amir
said by Anusha Ayyar Mumbai 11th May 2025