Can I ask you a question?
Of course you can.
Okay, can you get me out of this place?
I'm afraid I'm of no use to you there.
What?
Why couldn't they put me in a proper prison?
A better facility wasn't available.
A point made a muddlch.
It's a secure training centre.
Training?
What are the trainings for?
The other boys are screaming all the time.
And they've brought the problems forwards
and they shall work on it.
The other students all away from Corrid.
Why don't you go not every time you see my son-in-law school?
The second one is done.
What's the best place for you to be?
Ryan gets to stay at home until he's trialled.
Ryan is in the queues of such a series.
Apploved.
It's all accused.
If I did it, if I hurt her, then I get it.
But I didn't stand it, Jamie.
And this wasn't my decision.
I'm going to get it in the queue.
Nothing has been decided yet.
You know where it's going to be?
You're long in or so, my lord.
You need to sit down, Jamie.
If you don't sit down.
Does that mean you don't know?
Does that mean you don't know what you just want to tell me?
I think it's been decided yet.
You need to sit down.
Don't want to sit down.
If you don't sit down, I have to stop this discussion.
Maybe I want you to.
Do you?
It appears rough that wouldn't it?
You got to go home and then come back again.
Jamie, if you do not sit down.
Look, fucking want to sit down.
You, not.
Tell me where to sit down.
You do not control why, fuck.
Look at me now.
You do not control why I do in my life.
Get that in that fucking little idiot.
Fuck you now.